KEIICHI KATSUNO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



PERSONAL SKILLS

- Strong Independent Mind
- Great Emotional Awareness
- Proactivity and Responsibility
- Logical & Critical Thinking
- Problem-Solving
- Needs-Meeting

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby (Ruby on Rails)
- Javascript (React)
- UI/UX Design
- HTML5 / CSS / Bootstrap
- SQLite / PostgreSQL
- GitHub

LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Native)
- English (Professional)
- Spanish (Elementary)

INTERESTS

- Weight Training
- American Football
- Specialty Coffee
- Non-Fiction (e.g. Anthropology / History / Business etc)

CONTACT

20 Newton Street Kensington, Victoria 3031 045 255 3653 keichi031605@gmail.com

- My Portfolio: https://keiichi031605.github.io/ke iichi-portfolio/

PROFILE

Frontend & Ruby on Rails Developer. Deep interest in SaaS and passionate about business improvement that has a real influence on people's life.

My background came from outside of the tech field. For the past 6 years, I have engaged in Marketing and Relationship Development in Japan, and Production Management in the UK and Colombia. This journey has always been shaping my personality and growing my confidence to gain precious achievements individually. Now, I'm strongly competent in **Self Management** to overcome my personal issues and **Emotional Awareness** to emphasise to people for the problem-solving that are relevant to gaining organisational success in a team.

Of the motto in my life, I place a high value on **Respect** to people and **Proactivity** and **Responsibility** for my own achievements.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

Funeral Bookings, Melbourne, Australia | Jul 2020 - Present

- UI/UX Design
- Individual Collaboration for Project Management

QUALITY CONTROL INSPECTOR (INTERNSHIP)

InverCafé, Chinchiná, Colombia | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

- Deep Industrial Knowledge in Global Specialty Coffee Industry
- Products Analysis of Harvested Green Coffee Products
- Limited Working Proficiency of Spanish

PRODUCTION MANAGER (FULL-TIME)

The Roasting Shed, London, The UK | July 2018 - Sep 2019

- Production Development & Analysis of Specialty Coffee Products
- Market Research & Needs-Meeting for Clients
- Clients Support with Business English Proficiency

RELATIONSHIP MANAGER (FULL-TIME)

Yuasa Trading, Osaka & Fukuoka, Japan | Apr 2013 - July 2017

- Relationship Development with Stakeholders
- Project Management with a Team
- Sales, Marketing & Negotiation
- Account Management & Order Management

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, SPORTS MANAGEMENT

Kinki University, Osaka, Japan | Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

Outside of study, I engaged in an American Football club where I learned:

- Organisational Theory
- Leadership & Team Management and its difference
- Logical & Critical Thinking for Organisational Success.